

Syed Muhammad **Saglain**

Contact



+92 300 0580479



saglainprinters



Sle



saalain1020



//saalain1020 ms

Skills

React JS Material UI React Redux Persistence Routing

HTML5, CSS3 Javasciprt – ES6/ES7+ CSS/Canvas Animations

Firebase Hosting | Storage | CF Firestore | Authentication API Integration

Git, Github Object Oriented Programming

MongoDB NodeJS ExpressJS SocketIO

About me

I'm Saqlain an ambitious problem solver with a passion for learning and implementing new solutions, and who would like to join a team of like-minded developers. Experienced in creating logical and innovative solutions to complex problems.

My goal is to climb the ladder and become one of the leading experts in my field, and want to be a part of something bigger.

Education

2019-Current

BS:SE University of Karachi

201

Intermediate Adamjee Govt Science College

Matriculation

Work Experience

2020 - Current

Slectus (US)

Multivendor ecommerce style platform with commision support and a complex profile and product management system, MERN Stack App.

Role: Frontend Developer, responsible for all the frontend work and integrations on the platform, little backend development authorized.

2020 - 2020

Novasoft

Software House.

Role: Frontend Developer, responsible for most of the frontend work and integrations on their multiple projects in works.

1 Year

Al-Raheem Printing Services
Role: Graphics Designer

3rd Party Projects

Some of many third party app i have developed as a develope

NFT-Crypto web gops on ReactJS

Firebase Data and Auth applications Social Links sharing apps with NFC tag functionality

Many of my projects can be viewed on my webportfolio

Extras

Fiverr freelancing experience

- Webicamp module winner
- Graphics desiging from Arena Multimedia
- Contribution ICISCT 202
- Envoirment Modeling Workshop participation by Comstech of OIC